Guide to The Peter Dougherty Collection 1965 - 2001 MSS 213
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Audio
  - Subseries A: Audio, 1776-1785
    - VH1 15/6/94, June 15, 1994 (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0454)
      Sides A and B: Morning - 20 secs/10secs/5secs/2secs; Afternoon - 20 secs/10secs/5secs/2secs; Evening 1 - 20 secs/10secs/5secs/2secs; Evening 2 - 20 secs/10secs/5secs/2secs; Late Nite 1 - 20 secs/10secs/5secs/2secs; Late Nite 2 - 20 secs/10secs/5secs/2secs
      Container Annotation: © Picture Sounds Publishing 1994
      Tape Length: 50 minutes
    - Suicide Mudd Feb 6, 1979 (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0455)
      Side A: Lloyd Mud Jan 5, 1979 encore-late/Suicide Mud Feb 6, 1979
    - Suicide 57 Club Irving Plaza Sat. Jul 21 '79/CBGB 8-21-80, July 21, 1979/ August 21, 1980 (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0456)
      Sides A and B: Rocket U.S.A., Ghost Rider, Keep Your Dreams, Radiation, Harlem
    - Suicide Alan/with, Max's April 13 '79, Max's June 16, '80 w/ Wiseguys, Max's Nov 23 '80 w/ [Kramer], 1979-1980 (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0457)
      Side A: Touch Me, Ghost Rider, Keep Your Dreams, Four Horsemen, Rocket U.S.A. Sweetheart
    - Suicide Aug 25 '78 Max's (one set)/Judy Nylon Aug 27 '78 Max's (one set) w/ P. Pat Place, August 1978 (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0458)
      Side A: Ghost Rider, Rocket U.S.A., Cheree, Mr. Ray, Johnny, Harlem
      Side B: Unknown
    - Contortions Max's 10/12/78 only set/T.J. & Jerks Nov 4 '78 only set CBGB/Suicide Nov 4 '78 2nd Set CBGB. Dead Boys WPIX Oct 28 1978 (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0459)
      Side A: [Track Unknown], Disposable You, Dish it Out, [Track Unknown], Designed to Kill (x), [Track Unknown], Almost Black, [Track Unknown]
      Side B: Mr. Ray, Four Horsemen, 96 Tears, Harlem
    - Suicide Hurrah Sept 27 1978/Suicide Nov 1978 CBGB Nov. 3 1978 2nd set Nov. 4 1978 1st set (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0460)
      Side A: Ghost Rider, Mr. Ray, Keep Your Dreams, Las Vegas, [Track Unknown], 96 Tears, Harlem
      Side B: Dance, Las Vegas, 96 Tears, Harlem, Ghost Ride, Johnny, I Remember, Ghost Rider
    - Suicide CBGB 2/4/78, Max's 1/13/78/Contortions late show CBGB 2/4/78, 1978 (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0461)
      Side A: Dance, 96 Tears, Rocket U.S.A., Frankie, Dance, 96 Tears, Frankie
      Side B: I Don't Wanna Be Happy, My Infatuatino, Love Twice Removed, I'm Not a Bedroom Athlete, Jaded But So in Love, Roving Eye, Enjoy Yourself, Contort Yourself, Throw Me Away
    - The Cult 20 Oct '86, October 20, 1986 (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0462)
      Side A: Love Removal Machine, Wild Flower, Peace Dog, Aphrodisiac Jacket, Electric Ocean, Bad Fun
      Side B: Conquistador, Zap City, Love Trooper, Outlaw, Groove Co.
    - Doors LIVE Matrix San Francisco '67/ Roundhouse London '68, 1967-1968 (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0463)
      Side A: People Are Strange, Whiskey Bar, Crystal Ship, Unhappy Girl, Moonlight Drive, Summer's Almost Gone, 20th Century Fox, Backdoor Man, My Eyes Have Seen You, Soul Kitchen, Get Out of My Life Woman
      Side B: Light My Fire, Break on Thru, Five to One, The End, When the Music's Over
    - Suicide March 31 CBGB 2 sets/April 1 '78 one set/& Feb 4, 77 CBGB, 1977-1978 (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0464)
      Side A: Ghost Rider, Rocket U.S.A., Speed Queen, Harlem, Dance, Ghost Rider, 96 Tears, Frankie
      Side B: Rocket USA, Ghost Rider, Cheree, Frankie, 96 Tears/Rocket USA, Jesus
    - Big Youth/Clash/[Tramps] Sept 30 1980, September 30, 1980 (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0465)
      Side A: unknown
      Side B: Mag 7, Equalize, Call Up, Lose This Skin, Lightning, Up In Heaven, [Kingston] Advice, Mensforth Hill
    - Dread at the Control #2, undated (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0335)
    - Voidoids [Rev Kitchen] CBGB Oct 6 '77, October 6, 1977 (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0466)
      Sides A and B: Liars, Lose, Blank, Ventilator, Betrayal, Walkin'
    - Fleshtones, Zantees, Communists: Club 57 and Artists Space, April 7, 1978; May 2, 1978 (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0467)
    - The Fury Sound, undated (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0468)
    - Outer Limits: My Father's Place, June 7th, 1976 (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0469)
    - Patti Smith - Elgin, July 30, 1977 (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0470)
    - Patti Smith Live at the Other End, June 29, 1975 (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0471)
    - Raincoats TR3, May 16, 1980 (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0472)
    - Rap Party Riz, March 11, 1981 (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0473)
    - Shatki with J McLaughlin, June 28, 1976 (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0474)
    - Television Live CBGB, May 26, 1976 (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0475)
    - Television Live CBGB, January 23, 1976 (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0476)
    - Television Live CBGB, March 11, 1976 (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0477)
    - Wailers Live, June 18, 1975 (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0478)
    - Wailers Live at the Beacon Theatre, May 7, 1976 (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0479)
- Series II: Video / Film
  - Subseries A: Video
    - Stevie Wonder Tape 3, undated (Box 9, Media ID: 213.0354)
      Content: Crew talking after performance. Stevie Wonder does not appear on the disc.
      Format: 8mm Videocassette
      Access DVD available for researchers by appointment only.
    - [Untitled Compilation Tape], undated (Box 9, Media ID: 213.0355)
      Contents (Based on Container Annotation):
      Music Box, Coach to Paris, French T.V., Coach to Gig, Hippadrome Pre-Show, Island Special -U2, Bowie-->, Doherty's Donegal, [Malin] Head, British TV Fashion Show, Wilson's House, Tyrone Self Interview, Pontoon-John
    - Nelson George-Black Radio/Declaration of Independents, undated (Box 9, Media ID: 213.0356)
    - J.A. [Jefferson Airplane] Dick Cavett, Filmore Movie I, undated (Box 9, Media ID: 213.0357)
    - Videos, undated (Box 9, Media ID: 213.0358)
      Contents (based on Container Annotation):
      Joe Strummer "Gangsville", Suicide "Surrender" "Dominic", Capt Beefheart "Ice Cream For Crows", Murphy Law "Panty Raid", Bad Brains, Red Hot Chili "[white out] Ground", Bootsie!
    - Beastie Boy Guest V.J. Jan '87 Segments Promos, January 1987 (Box 9, Media ID: 213.0359)
    - Filmore II; Metallica; The Firm, undated (Box 9, Media ID: 213.0360)
    - '72 Rock n Roll, 1972 (Box 9, Media ID: 213.0361)
      1972 Flashback
    - Tom Petty-Cairo II, undated (Box 9, Media ID: 213.0362)
      MTV Caravan; Cairo Part II; Tom Petty
    - The Pogues Tokyo, Japan, undated (Box 9, Media ID: 213.0363)
    - Cairo 3 Sept '87, September 3, 1987 (Box 9, Media ID: 213.0364)
    - Roy Orbison/N. Chevry, undated (Box 9, Media ID: 213.0365)
      Pearl on "Wheel of Fortune"; Roy Orbison Rockumentary
      (Based on Container Annotation on label): Pearl on "Wheel", Roy Orbison,[Neehna Chevy]
      Pearl on "Wheel of Fortune"; Roy Orbison Rockumentary; On label: Pearl on "Wheel", Roy Orbison,[Neehna] Chevry
    - Stones; Motorhead, undated (Box 9, Media ID: 213.0366)
    - Club Mix/Fergus, undated (Box 9, Media ID: 213.0367)
      Club Mix show, Newcastle Co. Down, [Altered] Images, House of Lords; Fergus at St. James Gate
    - Ben Stiller, undated (Box 9, Media ID: 213.0368)
    - MTV Tom Petty & the Heartbreakers/MTV Winners Cairo, Egypt, September 2, 1987 (Box 9, Media ID: 213.0369)
    - Television, undated (Box 9, Media ID: 213.0370)
    - Spots - British Gaelic News, undated (Box 9, Media ID: 213.0371)
    - [Untitled Compilation Tape], undated (Box 9, Media ID: 213.0372)
      "Chase the Devil" P. Fonda, N.I. News, Toilet Interview
    - R 'n R Hall of Fame, undated (Box 9, Media ID: 213.0373)
    - Animation Celebration, undated (Box 9, Media ID: 213.0374)
    - [Untitled Compilation Tape], undated (Box 9, Media ID: 213.0375)
      Robert Townsend - HBO #2; "Black Shampoo"; Bootsy
    - Colin Quinn, undated (Box 9, Media ID: 213.0376)
      Shake Your Rump, Colin Quinn Special, Steve Wright Special, Simpsons
    - Rodger Waters, undated (Box 9, Media ID: 213.0377)
    - Smiths Live Paris, undated (Box 9, Media ID: 213.0378)
    - Pogues: White City, undated (Box 10, Media ID: 213.0379)
      Format: 8mm Videocassette - PAL Standard
      Pogues: Cotton Fields Video
    - Captain Beefheart MTV Networks, Inc.: 60, undated (Box 10, Media ID: 213.0380)
      [Label Reads:] MTV Networks, Inc. Captain Beefheart :60 Regen A.T.T.C.
    - Jean-Michel Basquiat - Art Breaks, undated (Box 10, Media ID: 213.0381)
      [Label Reads:] JMB - PD "Jean-Michel Basquiat" Art Breaks Prod. By: MTV Networks, Inc. 11/27/85
      [Label on white cardboard box]
    - Captain Beefheart "Ice Cream for Crow", undated (Box 10, Media ID: 213.0382)
      [Label Reads:] MTV Networks Captain Beefheart "Ice Cream for Crow" 5:00 Time Code Trk 3 Regen 2/9/90
    - The Pogues, City Gardens, Trenton, NJ, September 25, 1987 (Box 9, Media ID: 213.0383)
      Original Format: Video 8mm
      TRT: 01:04:44
    - The Pogues, Croke Park, June 27, 1987 (Box 9, Media ID: 213.0384)
      TRT: 00:42:17
    - Pogues Dressing Room Backstage, P.T.A., June 27, 1987 (Box 9, Media ID: 213.0385)
      Contents (based on Container Annotation): From Channel 4 Documentary P.T.A.
      TRT: 01:03:50
    - Pogues Paris Hippodrome 4 July '87, July 4, 1987 (Box 9, Media ID: 213.0386)
      TRT: 01:04:03
    - The Pogues - Sullivan Stadium - Foxboro, Mass. 22 Sept. '87, September 22, 1987 (Box 9, Media ID: 213.0387)
      TRT: 01:27:05
    - The Pogues, Japan, undated (Box 9, Media ID: 213.0389)
      TRT: 01:31:25
    - Clash/B.A.D., undated (Box 9, Media ID: 213.0390)
      Contents (based on Container Annotation): Clash Special, Clash on Broadway, Bottom Line [Nico], B.A.D. on MTV July '84
      TRT: 01:54:49
    - Hip Hop #1, undated (Box 9, Media ID: 213.0391)
      Contents (based on Container Annotation): "8 Wonder" - Sugarhill, Roxanne Shanté, Whodini, Run DMC V.J.'s
      TRT: 01:11:18
    - Midnight Special, undated (Box 9, Media ID: 213.0392)
      Contents (based on Container Annotation): Sinead O'Connor Unplugged Midnight Special, Suicide, Iggy, Cars, Led Zeppelin, Old/New
      TRT: 01:12:52
    - Captain Beefheart-Van-Little Feat, undated (Box 9, Media ID: 213.0393)
      Contents (based on Container Annotation): Captain Beefheart - Lick My Decals Off Baby, Ice Cream for Crow; Van Morrison- Tupelo Honey, Moondance; Little Feat - Domino; That Petrol Emotion; Pogues stories
      TRT: 00:52:28
    - "Days of Rage", undated (Box 9, Media ID: 213.0397)
      TRT: 02:07:24
    - The Pogues Hollywood Palladium L.A., 11 Dec '87, December 11, 1987 (Box 9, Media ID: 213.0399)
      TRT: 00:36:51
    - MTV Cokes- Barcelona, undated (Box 9, Media ID: 213.0400)
- Series III: MTV and Music Business
  This series documents Dougherty's work as Creative Director for MTV Europe. Branding and programming materials are arranged chronologically while artists files are arranged alphabetically.
  - Subseries A: Branding and Programming
    - MTV Music Television Whos' Who in Rock Video: A Guide to Video Music Artists, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Easy E and Tommy Boy Letters Re: MTV Raps, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Angie Li, MTV Director of On Air Promotion Announcement, June 22, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Ed Lover and Doctor Dre Press Pack, April, November 1994 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - 1st MTV European Music Awards Program, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - MTV Video Music Awards Program, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - MTV Europe Music Awards Post Show Party Invitation, November 23, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - MTV Europe Music Awards Program, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - MTV Youth Catalog with Video Music Awards Information, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - WORM (Word of Relevant Mouth): European Youth Market Conference Booklet [2], 1996 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - do 84: ever-changing brand development @ KesselsKramer, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - MTV Headbangers Ball, Chaos Ad: Rock in the 90's by Steve Beebee with a foreword by Vanessa Warwick, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - MTV-Cyclopedia: The Official MTV Guide to the Hottest Bands, Stars, Events, and Music by Nick Duerden, Ian Gittins, and Shaun Phillips, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - MTV Operators Manual, April 27, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - MTV Video Music Awards Program, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - MTV:UK User Manual, August 10, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - MTV Networks Europe Policy and Procedures Manual: UK, September 1999 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - MTV Europe Music Awards Program, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - MTV Europe Music Awards: Stockholm Program, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - MTV Research: Pictures of Youth, Results from Youth Research, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - "Eric's Very Basic Guide to Music Television" [Manuscript], 2000 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - MTV Media Pan European Trade Website Launch Pack, January 2001 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - "Glory Days" and "New Series for MTV...What's New?" by Aimaq Rapp Stolle, May 2001 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Boris Zhubov Letter Re: MTV Logo, April 3, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - MTV Logo Photographs, undated (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - MTV Networks Digital Channels: The Strategic Route to Genre Segmentation, undated (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - The MTV Premium Catalog: Clothing and Accessories, undated (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - "Brian Eno: MTV Ideas (figurative, narrative)", undated (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - MTV Event Passes, various (Binder 1)
    - MTV Raps ProSet MusiCards 1, 1991 (Box 15, Object ID: 213.2.0001)
    - MTV Raps ProSet MusiCards 2, 1991 (Box 15, Object ID: 213.2.0002)
  - Subseries B: Artists Files
    - Beastie Boys: "Home Video" Financial Documents, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Beastie Boys: Licensed to Ill Tour with Fishbone and Murphy's Law Handbooks [3], 1987 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Beastie Boys: "She's Crafty" and "Rhymin' and Stealin' " Financial Documents, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Beastie Boys: "She's Crafty" and "Rhymin' and Stealin' " Production Scripts [1 of 2], 1987 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Beastie Boys: "She's Crafty" and "Rhymin' and Stealin' " Production Scripts [2 of 2], 1987 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - "Beastie Sit/com": "Beasties Get Ill" a teleplay by Adam C. Dubin for Def Jam Visuals [Manuscript], November 19, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Beastie Boys: '99 Europe Tour Handbook, April - May 1999 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - LL Cool J: Promo Spot Invoices, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Oasis: Images, undated (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Pogues: "Fairytale of New York" Financial Documents, 1987 - 1988 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Pogues / Danzig: "Self-Aid Make It Work" Event, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Pogues: Set List, undated (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Pogues: "White City / Misty Morning" Video Call Sheets, Production Notes, October 1989 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Run DMC and Beastie Boys with Special Appearances by Davy D. [Press Pack], 1987 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Run DMC and Beastie Boys: Together Forever Tour Financial Documents, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Run DMC: "Tougher Than Leather" Screenplay by Ric Menello and Rick Rubin, Based on a Story by Lyor Cohen, Bill Adler, and Ric Menello [Manuscript], undated (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Run DMC and Beastie Boys: World Tour Handbook [With Annotations, 2], 1987 (Box 13, Folder 22)
- Series IV: Ephemera, Flyers, Programs
  This series documents Dougherty's personal and professional collection of music, art, and film event ephemera in the form of flyers, invitations, posters, programs, and ticket stubs. Each subseries is organized alphabetically by artist, venue, or document type.
  - Subseries A: Music
    - Bruce Springsteen: Autograph, undated (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - CBGB: Erasers, Feelies, Steel Tips, Suicide, undated (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - The Clash: Flyers and Lyrics, June 1, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - The Clash: T-Shirt, undated (Box 15, Object ID: 213.2.0003)
    - Club 57, February 2, 1979; undated (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - The Cramps, undated (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - [Flyers and Clippings], various (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - George Michael: "Fastlove/Older" - Images, undated (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Heartbreakers / Johnny Thunders, November 30th [no year] (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Hurrah: Walter Steding and the Dragon People, DNA, November 27th [no year] (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - Iron Maiden: Europe Tour Book, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - Masters of Reality, 1984; undated (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - Max's Kansas City: Contortions, Von LMO, Feelies, Levi & the Rockats, 1978; undated (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - Mudd Club, May 22, 1980; undated (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - Patti Smith, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - Public Image Limited, 1983; undated (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - Ramones, undated (Box 13, Folder 38)
    - Roxy Club [London & NYC], 1982 (Box 13, Folder 39)
    - Roxy Music with the Sadistic Mika Band Program; Bryan Ferry Press Shots from D. Letts, Autumn 1975; March 1976 (Box 13, Folder 40)
    - Slayer: Decade of Aggression Live Album Pamphlet, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 41)
    - Slits, January 18, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 42)
    - VIP Passes and Ticket Stubs [1 of 3], various (Binder 2)
    - VIP Passes and Ticket Stubs [2 of 3], various (Binder 3)
    - VIP Passes and Ticket Stubs [3 of 3], various (Binder 4)
    - Whiz Kid and Afrika Bambaataa: Dance Music Report, undated (Box 13, Folder 43)
    - ZZ Top: Official Key Chain, 1985 (Box 15, Object ID: 213.2.0004)
  - Subseries B: Art
    - 51X Gallery, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 44)
    - Area, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 45)
    - Brooke Alexander, 1985 - 1986 (Box 13, Folder 46)
    - Danceteria, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 47)
    - Executive Gallery, 1983 - 1984 (Box 13, Folder 48)
    - [Exhibition Invitations], various (Box 13, Folder 49)
    - Fun Gallery, 1983 - 1985 (Box 13, Folder 50)
    - The Hospital: Yes Yes Y'all Private View Notebook, October 23, 2003 (Box 13, Folder 51)
    - Jane Dickson, 1996, 2001, 2005 (Box 13, Folder 52)
    - Robert Williams, 1990, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 53)
  - Subseries C: Animation and Film
    - Anamu Animation Directory, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 54)
    - Animated Film: Federal Republic of Germany, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 55)
    - Animerte Dager: Den fjerde internasjonale Oslo Animation Festival Program, April 24 - 27, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 56)
    - British Animation Awards: Baa! Catalog, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - [Commercial Animation and Film Flyers, Pamphlets], various (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Holland Animation Film Festival Program, November 1994 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Holland Animation Film Festival Program, November 1996 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Holland Animation Film Festival Program [2], November 1998 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - International Animated Film Festival: Annecy, Haute-Savoie, France Program, June 1 - 6, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - International Animated Film Festival: Annecy, Haute-Savoie, France Program, May 31 - June 5, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - International Animation Festival: Cardiff, Wales Program, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - International Animation Festival: Cardiff, Wales Program, May 27 - June 1, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - International Animation Festival: Cardiff, Wales Program, June 1998 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - 15th International Festival of Film and Television in the Celtic Countries Program, March 28 - April 1, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - 4th International Short Film Festival: Curtas-Metragens Vila do Conde, Portugal Program, July 2 - 7, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - 19th International Short Film Festival: Hamburg, Germany Program, June 4 - 9, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Naturama: Environmental Video Contest Program, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Ottawa International Student Animation Festival, October 21 - 24, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Summer in Japan: A Film at the Public Presentation in Cooperation with Japan Society Program, Summer 1982 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Vida Artificial Life: Exposition Barcelona Art Futura (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Video Art Plastique: Herouville Saint-Clair Program, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Video Pop Combo Festival Program, April 1992 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - West Surrey College of Art and Design (WSCAD): Farnham Animation Guide, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 20)
- Series V: Personal
  This series contains personal items and collectibles organized alphabetically by document type.
  - Artifacts, Business Cards, undated (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, 1986 - 1987, 1992, undated (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - For the Students of Ithaca Notebook, undated (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Hells Angels Forever Calendar, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Housing File, 1988 - 1989 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Travel File, 1980s - 1990s (Box 14, Folder 27)
- OVERSIZE Series III: MTV and Music Business
  - Subseries A: Branding and Programming
    - [Quake] Graffiti MTV Collage on Netherlands Map, undated (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Subseries B: Artists Files
    - Tone Loc: "Hasta la vista, Baby" Transparency, 1988 - 1989 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- OVERSIZE Series IV: Ephemera, Flyers, Programs
  - Subseries A: Music
    - CBGB: The B-52s, DNA, Erasers, Feelies, Nervus Rex, Terminal Posters, various (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - [Clippings], various (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Club 57 / Irving Plaza: The B-52s, Contortions, Crass, The Cramps, Stimulators, Suicide, Walter Stedding Posters, various (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Danzig: Video Shoot Flyer, November 9th [no year] (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Hurrah: The B-52s, The Cramps, DNA, Walter Steding & the Dragon People, various (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - The Kitchen: Love of Life Orchestra with Martin Rev; Daily Life, The Gynecologists, Theoretical Girls, Arsenal Posters, April 9; April 19th [no years] (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Max's Kansas City: The B-52s, The Cramps, Judy Nylon, Nervus Rex, Richard Hell & the Voidoids, Teenage Jesus and the Jerks, Von LMO, various (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Music Posters, 1974 - 1985, undated (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - "You Can't Say 'Fuck' in Radio Free America" by Patti Smith, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Subseries B: Art
    - 6 Artists from the East Village on Main Street Poster, December 6 - 10, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Jan Van Eyck Academie Discussion Workshop Poster, April 25, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Subseries C: Animation and Film
    - D&AD Awards 1999 Published by Creative Review (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Film Posters: The Blank Generation, Gang War, Order of Death, 1980, 1983, undated (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Music, Art & Film Posters: "Copkiller," Evening Standard "My Father Shot Kennedy," "The Genealogy of Contemporary Rock Radio," Slits, Still Graffiti, various (Map-case 5.E)